WHEN THE WALLS FALL DOWN
It's Eva! Something's happened to her!
Mama!
Mama... Flopin...
Yugo the Eliatrope, protect your friends.
And if you survive,
watch out for the Enutrof.
Dathura, hold on!
That can't be anything good.
Please untie me, darling.
I will consider untying you...
if you give me a passionate kiss.
Eva...
Any idea what's going on, Oropo?
A powerful spirit,
perhaps a spirit more powerful than me...
It could destroy everything.
Mama!
-It's the baby.
-Is it okay?
Yes, don't worry. I feel it moving.
But you were hit by a spell.
Don't you think you need to...?
It's close now.
Flopin!
Untie me so I can help your mother.
Give me one good reason to trust you.
All you need to know right now
is that I'm an Eniripsa,
and if I help her,
there's a chance everything will go well.
Flopin!
If you don't keep your promise,
I will make you pay.
Flopin, your kind spirit is what will
make you an excellent Cra god.
Threats don't suit you.
So, let's do this.
I thought this place
was under your control.
It is, but it doesn't seem
to suit everyone.
Any idea what's happening?
An ultra-powerful being is destroying
our dimension.
There are more surprises in store for us.
I need your help.
Tell me what to do.
I'm going to try to contain
the destruction of the tower.
Our entire mission depends on it.
I'll find out who's responsible
and stop them... by any means necessary.
It's coming from Sram level.
I'll take care of it.
Keep breathing.
I'll try and stop the pain for you.
Thank you.
Well, this is a surprise.
Is Evangelyne causing all of this?
Actually, it's her baby.
Adamai, just leave us alone.
It's complicated enough.
Help Oropo instead.
I imagine he has a lot on his plate.
You guys are quite the family.
Stay away from my mother,
or you'll regret it.
We'll have to have
this conversation later.
Now, let's call a short truce
until things are resolved.
I'm not in... any position
to suggest anything else.
Good luck, then, Evangelyne!
Thank you, Adamai.
Stay with us, Evangelyne.
Flopin, keep your mother awake,
she has to keep pushing.
-But...
-Do you hear me, Flopin?
She mustn't pass out,
otherwise we'll lose them both.
Dathura seems to have
a grudge against you.
Yeah, who knows what that's about?
All of this has something to do
with my mom.
I can't explain it, but I'm sure of it.
Well?
It's Evangelyne.
-What does she have to do with it?
-She's giving birth.
It seems the baby is responsible
for everything.
Of course, the child of a former god
wouldn't be anything less than a demigod.
In the meantime, we need to find
a way to calm its spirit,
or it will destroy everything.
I'm going to need you, Ad.
What do you want me to do?
Help me, lend me
some of the Eliatrope Dofus powers,
so I can support the baby's spirit.
Gently, Ad, I can't endure as much as you.
Very good,
I will try to reconstruct the tower.
Flopin, you can't let your mother faint.
No, but I... All right, fine, then.
Did you seriously just slap me?
For your own good, Mama,
you have to stay awake.
Stay as strong as you can.
We're counting on you.
Give me your hand.
Your father's not even here for this.
He's got another thing coming!
I'm going to count to three,
then push with everything you've got.
All right.
One... Two... Three! Push hard now!
I see the head. Push again!
Come on, Mama, you can do it!
A test of willpower against a newborn.
If it didn't hurt so much, it'd be funny.
Hold on, Oropo!
You know
it could be a lot worse than this.
You're in less danger
without the Dofus in your body.
Thank you. Thank you, Dathura.
We'd have all been goners without you.
Any idea what's going on?
This world was created by Oropo.
He made it using the Eliacube
and the strength of his spirit.
In a way, we're all his guests.
No one can find us here.
But why is everything falling apart?
Because a powerful and tormented spirit
is threatening this dimension's existence.
As for him, I tried to warn you.
-He's not your friend.
-Yeah, I've known that for a while.
Ruel cares a lot about money, but...
Hang on, Evangelyne, almost there.
A new demigod has entered the family.
He's so cute!
It's going to be two against three
at home now, my love.
You're off to a good start.
If you're anything like them,
a good meal will calm you down.
Thank you for everything you've done,
Echo.
Without you,
I don't know what would have happened.
We're even. I don't know what Toxine
would have done without your help.
It's over. That was a really close call.
The Sadlygroves, what a family.
Yes, indeed.
I'll have to rebuild something
a little more practical.
Lend me some more of your strength,
brother.
My underwear, my underwear!
Anything but my underwear!
That was a very passionate kiss.
So, you'll untie me now, right?
No!
It's falling, without falling.
Perper, you've always been such a poet.
Do you hear that?
Sort of. Is someone beating a pig?
-Dally, don't you get it?
-Get what?
Wasn't someone ready to pop
like a barrel of bamboo milk
last time you saw her?
-Oh! It's my baby!
-Typical.
You could have said something earlier,
idiot!
Hey, Gou, do you have enough strength
to throw me high enough to see?
It's worth a try.
Look, Mama!
Throw me that way, halfway.
There's a new addition to the family!
Look over there!
It's my dad!
Hold on, Elely.
They're all the same in that family.
We've got nothing better to do,
so let's follow her.
Dathura, I'd like to see you again.
You know where to find me, Amalia.
Dathura, Oropo is going to be very angry.
You're not being helpful.
You're too stupid to see
what he's capable of. He'll do anything.
You are extremely ungrateful
for everything he did for us.
He saved all of our lives.
Before he asked us to join him,
we were nothing.
Now he's in the process of transforming us
into the new gods.
Why do you think we'll be better off?
All I need to know is
he believes in this mission.
It's called having a bit of faith
in others.
Eva!
Careful, you Iopbrain.
Aw, a baby Iop.
His first punch!
No, he punched me first!
Dally, without Flopin helping me,
it could have turned out pretty bad.
Come here, you little mama's boy.
Mama! Papa!
Be careful, Iopbrain!
That couldn't have been Ruel, no way.
I'm almost finished now.
Just a little more.
At last.
-You, but...
-You're here!
You're close enough to touch.
How I've dreamed of you.
Yugo?